MUHAMAD HUSNI RAMADHAN

Kandang Roda no.31 Kec. Cibinong Kab, Bogor 16912 081299300735

husniramadhan97@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Web Developers are experienced in following established procedures and working under little or no supervision. Offers technical expertise in programming analysis, application analysis and design. Outstanding team excellent team with in-depth knowledge of development tools and languages.

HTML and XML

SKILLS

Java Script

Conceptual Understanding UX Design

Web-based software engineering Problem Solving

React Js

MYSQL

SEO AND Copywriting

EDUCATION

S1 Informatics Engineering

Universitas Pamulang, Kota Tanggerang Selatan

IPK - 3.47

MAN 1 Bogor (Cibinong)

2012 - 2015

2019 - 2023

Jl. Kayu Manis, Cirimekar, Kec. Cibinong, Kabupaten Bogor, Jawa Barat 16917

EXPERIENCE

PT Multi Daya Insani

WEB Developer

01/09/ 2022 - 31/11/2022

- Designing, implementing drug data applications for human gem clinics
- Provides high availability and performance
- · Contribute in all phases of the development cycle
- · Write well-designed, efficient, and testable code
- Perform software analysis, programming, testing, and debug
- Investigate alternatives and technologies
- · Presentation for architectural review

PT. Araki Solusi Indonesia

WEB Developer and Digital Marketing

01/12/2022 - 01/11/2023

- Design, develop and implement software applications for websites based on analyzed requirements and an understanding of industry technical standards.
- needs that have been analyzed and an understanding of industry technical standards.
- Create Company Profile Website of PT Araki Solusi Indonesia and PT Berka Elektrik Indonesia.
- Create data analysis of website and social media traffic development levels
- · Manage digital marketing campaigns, including SEO, social media, and email marketing
- Assist in writing marketing content such as feed descriptions, video content creation and other promotional materials.
- Conduct market analysis and competitor research to support marketing strategy development

CERTIFICATION

12/2021 - Junior Web Developer by BNSP Kominfo

03/2022 - Digital Marketing by Asosiasi Digital Marketing Indonesia (DIGIMIND)

06/2022 - Data Management Staff by BNSP Kominfo